Guide to the Mabel Loomis Todd Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1879-1932; Series II; 14 linear feet (33 boxes)
  - General Correspondence
    - Packard, Harriet M., 1894, undated (Box 20, Folder 535)
    - Palmer, Alice Freeman (Mrs. George H.), 1897-1902, undated (Box 20, Folder 536-538)
    - Palmer, Emily J., 1897-1927, undated (Box 20, Folder 539)
    - Palmer, Frederic (Box 20, Folder 539)
    - Palmer, Frederic, Jr. (Box 20, Folder 539)
    - Palmer, George H., 1888-1923 (Box 20, Folder 540-542)
    - Palmer, Marry F., 1919-1924, undated (Box 20, Folder 543)
    - Paros, Rosa Mercedy, 1907-1909 (Box 20, Folder 544)
    - Parsons, Anna A., 1908-1910 (Box 20, Folder 545)
    - Patterson, Jane Adams, 1909, undated (Box 20, Folder 546)
    - Peirce, Lydia P. Ray, 1900-1924 (Box 20, Folder 547)
    - Pemberton, John, 1896 (Box 20, Folder 548)
    - Ph-Pu, 1887-1932 (Box 20, Folder 549)
    - Photographic Times, 1897-1904 (Box 20, Folder 550)
    - Pickering, Edward, 1892, 1897, 1906, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 551)
    - Pickering, L.S. (Mrs. Edward), 1889-1911 (Box 20, Folder 552-553)
    - Pohl, Josephine Pollitt, 1924-1930 (Box 20, Folder 554)
      See also: box 12, folder 248.
    - Polk, Grace Porterfield, 1923-1930 (Box 20, Folder 555)
    - Poole, Fanny, 1886, 1888 (Box 20, Folder 556)
    - Pope, Abby Lindee, 1898 (Box 20, Folder 557)
    - Pope, Albert A. (Box 20, Folder 557)
    - Pope, Amelia Dickinson, 1906, undated (Box 20, Folder 558)
    - Pope, Anna Dickinson (Box 20, Folder 558)
    - Pope, Amy Stoughton, 1900, 1901 (Box 20, Folder 559)
    - Pope, Leonard W. (Box 20, Folder 559)
    - Pope, Clara, 1881-1884 (Box 20, Folder 560)
    - Powell, Adele G., Undated (Box 20, Folder 561)
    - Prentice, Doris E., 1923-1931 (Box 20, Folder 562)
    - Prentiss, Caroline (Mrs. George H.), 1889-1927, undated (Box 20, Folder 563-566)
    - Proctor, Mary, 1899-1906 (Box 20, Folder 567)
    - Purrington, Anna C. (Mrs. William A.), 1905-1919, undated (Box 20, Folder 568)
    - Purrington, William A. (Box 20, Folder 568)
    - Q, 1916, 1917 (Box 20, Folder 569)
    - Ra-Ri, 1888-1928 (Box 20, Folder 570)
    - Ransom, Alice Ruth (Mrs. Paul C.), 1917-1931 (Box 20, Folder 571)
    - Raymond, Marion, 1888-1890 (Box 20, Folder 572)
    - Reily, Mabel Downes (Mrs. Phil Key), 1879-1907 (Box 20, Folder 573)
    - Rice, Mrs. Ellen F., 1904-1905 (Box 20, Folder 574)
    - Rice, Mrs. Ellen F., 1906-1908, undated (Box 21, Folder 575-576)
    - Richards, Laura E., 1911-1913 (Box 21, Folder 577)
    - Ro, 1889-1932 (Box 21, Folder 578)
    - Robinson, Elizabeth (Mrs. Edward), 1890-1898, undated (Box 21, Folder 579-580)
    - Robinson, S.A.K., Circa1880-1910 (Box 21, Folder 581)
    - Rockwell, Marion B., 1903-1930 (Box 21, Folder 582)
    - Rogers, Clara K. (Mrs. Henry M.), 1907-1921, undated (Box 21, Folder 583)
    - Rogers, Henry M. (Box 21, Folder 583)
    - Rolfe, W.J., 1894, 1909, undated (Box 21, Folder 584)
    - Root, Fanny A., 1890-1895 (Box 21, Folder 585)
    - Rosenwald, Julius, 1918 (Box 21, Folder 586)
    - Ross-Brown, Henrietta F. (Mrs. Albert), 1918-1932, undated (Box 21, Folder 587-588)
    - Rotch, A. Lawrence, Circa 1895-1912 (Box 21, Folder 589)
    - Rotch, Margaret (Box 21, Folder 589)
    - Ru, 1891-1919, undated (Box 21, Folder 590)
    - Runkle, L.J., 1912, undated (Box 21, Folder 591)
    - Rusch, Florence D., 1905, 1915, 1923, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 592)
    - Rusch, Henry A. (Box 21, Folder 592)
    - Russell, Celeste S., 1899-1912, undated (Box 21, Folder 593)
    - Russell, Clara (Box 21, Folder 593)
    - Russell, M., 1892, 1896 (Box 21, Folder 594)
    - Rutherford, Cora (Mrs. John), 1920 (Box 21, Folder 595)
    - Ryan, Anna A., 1922, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 596)
    - Rybier, Felicia, 1927-1932, undated (Box 21, Folder 597)
    - Sa-Sc, 1882-1932 (Box 21, Folder 598)
    - Saint-Gaudens, Augusta Homer, 1919-1925 (Box 21, Folder 599)
    - Saint-Gaudens, Homer (Box 21, Folder 599)
    - Sanborn, Kate, 1906, 1907 (Box 21, Folder 600)
    - Sawyer, Elizabeth Coffin, 1899-1924, undated (Box 21, Folder 601-605)
    - Sawyer, Lesley Tobey (Mrs. Edward), 1898-1906, undated (Box 21, Folder 606)
    - Schauffler, W.G., 1889 (Box 21, Folder 607)
    - Schiff, Adele G., 1906, undated (Box 21, Folder 608)
    - Schiff, Frieda, 1894 (Box 21, Folder 609)
    - Schiff, Jacob H., 1894-1919, undated (Box 21, Folder 610-611)
    - Schiff, Mortimer L., 1884-1931 (Box 21, Folder 612)
    - Schiff, Therese (Mrs. Jacob), 1893, 1898, 1899, 1905, 1909, 1913, undated (Box 21, Folder 613)
    - Schmidtlein, Hedwig, 1910 (Box 21, Folder 614)
    - Schneider, Ila Roberts, 1905-1910, undated (Box 21, Folder 615)
    - Schroder, Olga M.D., 1895 (Box 21, Folder 616)
    - Scudder, Samuel H., 1888-1897 (Box 21, Folder 617)
    - Se-Sh, 1883-1932 (Box 21, Folder 618)
    - Seelye, Abby Taylor, 1880-1895, undated (Box 21, Folder 619)
    - Seelye, Anna H. (Box 21, Folder 619)
    - Seelye, Elizabeth J. (Box 21, Folder 619)
    - Seelye, L.C. (Box 21, Folder 619)
    - Seelye, Lucile H. (Box 21, Folder 619)
    - Seligman, Gerta, 1900-1930 (Box 21, Folder 620)
    - Seligman, Isaac (Box 21, Folder 620)
    - Seligman, Isaiah (Box 21, Folder 620)
    - Sewall, May Wright, 1904-1920 (Box 21, Folder 621)
    - Shephard Stores of Boston, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 622)
    - Si-Sl, 1893-1925 (Box 21, Folder 623)
    - Slade, A.J., 1912-1928 (Box 21, Folder 624)
    - Slade, Elizabeth A. (Box 21, Folder 624)
    - Slade, Mary Clothier (Mrs. Alexander) (Box 21, Folder 624)
    - Slade, Ida, 1911-1932 (Box 22, Folder 625-28)
    - Sm, 1889-1929 (Box 22, Folder 629)
    - Smith, Adela Wood, 1906, undated (Box 22, Folder 630)
    - Smith, Anna M. (Mrs. Henry P.), 1904, 1907, 1908, 1913, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 631)
    - Smith, Bessie, 1883 (Box 22, Folder 632)
    - Smith, Ellen, 1888-1891 (Box 22, Folder 633)
    - Smith, H. Kirk, 1910, 1911 (Box 22, Folder 634)
    - Smith, Henry Preserved, 1899, 1901 (Box 22, Folder 635)
    - Smith, Rose Eliot (Mrs. Holmes), 1932 (Box 22, Folder 636)
    - Smith, Winifred, 1902, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 637)
    - Sneath, Laura S. (Mrs. Samuel B.), 1904-1923, undated (Box 22, Folder 638)
    - Snell, Sabra C., 1917-1920 (Box 22, Folder 639)
    - So-Sp, 1893-1931 (Box 22, Folder 640)
    - Soper, Effie May, 1922-1925 (Box 22, Folder 641)
    - Soper, Harold (Box 22, Folder 641)
    - Sprague, David, 1906-1917, undated (Box 22, Folder 642)
    - St, 1893-1930 (Box 22, Folder 643)
    - Starr, Agnes M., 1899-1910 (Box 22, Folder 644)
    - Starr, Martha W. (Box 22, Folder 644)
    - Stearns, Alfred E., 1895-1932 (Box 22, Folder 645-646)
    - Stearns, Arthur F., 1909-1911, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 647)
    - Stearns, Kate E. (Mrs. Arthur F.), 1919, undated (Box 22, Folder 648)
    - Stearns, Mary E. Kittredge (Mrs. William F.), 1886-1903, undated (Box 22, Folder 649-650)
    - Stearns, Olive Coit (Mrs. William A.), Undated (Box 22, Folder 651)
    - Mrs. Stearns' School, "The Convent", 1885 (Box 22, Folder 652)
    - Sterrett, J.R.S., 1892, 1893, undated (Box 22, Folder 653)
    - Sterrett, Josephine Quarrier (Mrs. J.R.S.) (Box 22, Folder 653)
    - Stetson, Marian, 1922-1927 (Box 23, Folder 654)
    - Stone, Anna B., 1899, 1902 (Box 23, Folder 655)
    - Stone, Mrs. C.E. Whiton, 1895-1912, undated (Box 23, Folder 656-658)
    - Stone, Harlan F., 1928 (Box 23, Folder 659)
    - Storrs, Mary E. (Mrs. R.S.), 1888-1895, undated (Box 23, Folder 660-661)
    - Story, E.M., Circa 1880-1893, undated (Box 23, Folder 662)
    - Story, Oliver Howard (Box 23, Folder 662)
    - Stricklett, Helen (Mrs. Morgan), 1925-1929 (Box 23, Folder 663)
    - Stricklett, Morgan (Box 23, Folder 663)
    - Strong, Mary E. (Mrs. Alexander), 1892-1911, undated (Box 23, Folder 664)
    - Su-Sy, 1900-1932 (Box 23, Folder 665)
    - Sullivan, Florence S., 1900, 1901, undated (Box 23, Folder 666)
    - Sweetser, Cornelia P., Circa 1880-1932 (Box 23, Folder 667)
    - Sweetser, Jeanette (Box 23, Folder 667)
    - Sweetser, Kate Dickinson (Box 23, Folder 667)
    - Swift, Carrie D.T. (Mrs. Lewis), 1892-1896 (Box 23, Folder 668)
    - Symington, W. Stuart, Jr., Undated (Box 23, Folder 669)
    - Ta-Th, 1888-1928 (Box 23, Folder 670)
    - Taggard, Genevieve, Undated (Box 23, Folder 671)
    - Talcott, Fanny C., 1898, 1909 (Box 23, Folder 672)
    - Taylor, James M., 1897, 1912 (Box 23, Folder 673)
    - Tenney, Julia, [188?], 1927 (Box 23, Folder 674)
    - Tenney, Robert B. (Box 23, Folder 674)
    - Thaw, Mary C.(Mrs. William), 1902-1921, undated (Box 23, Folder 675)
    - Thomas, Katherine, 1901 (Box 23, Folder 676)
    - Thompson, Daniel, 1916-1923 (Box 23, Folder 677)
    - Thompson, Daniel V. (Box 23, Folder 677)
    - Thompson, Randall (Box 23, Folder 677)
    - Thompson, Betty, 1931 (Box 23, Folder 678)
    - Thoreau, Maria, 1879 (Box 23, Folder 679)
      See also: box 1, folder 33.
    - Thursby, Emma Cecelia, 1921-1929 (Box 23, Folder 680)
    - Thurshy, Ina L., 1921-1932 (Box 23, Folder 681)
    - Thwing, Charles F., 1904-1913 (Box 23, Folder 682)
    - Ti-Tu, 1885-1929 (Box 23, Folder 683)
    - Todt, Arthur L., 1910, undated (Box 23, Folder 684)
    - Todt, Margaret Lovejoy (Box 23, Folder 684)
    - Toll, Charles H., 1919-1928, undated (Box 23, Folder 685)
    - Toll, Mayes M. (Mrs. Charles H.) (Box 23, Folder 685)
    - Tolstoy, Count Ilya, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 686)
    - Torrence, Josephine M., 1925-1930 (Box 23, Folder 687)
    - Torrence, Katharine, 1926, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 688)
    - Trapp, Armenia B. Hobart (Mrs. Harlan A.), 1925-1928, undated (Box 23, Folder 689)
    - Trow, C.G., 1895-1898 (Box 23, Folder 690)
    - Trow, Geneva A. (Box 23, Folder 690)
    - Tsuda, Ume (Mrs. George), 1898, 1899 (Box 23, Folder 691)
    - Tucker, H.G., 1884-1910 (Box 23, Folder 692)
    - Tucker, Jeannie D. (Mrs. H.G.) (Box 23, Folder 692)
    - Tuesday Morning Club, Circa 1917 (Box 23, Folder 693)
    - Twiss, Stephen P., 1898-1910 (Box 23, Folder 694)
    - Tyler, B.S., Circa 1880, 1893 (Box 23, Folder 695)
    - U, 1900-1911, undated (Box 23, Folder 696)
    - Untermeyer, Louis, 1930, 1931 (Box 23, Folder 697)
    - V, 1887-1930 (Box 24, Folder 698)
    - Vorse, Mary Heaton, Circa 1880, 1910 (Box 24, Folder 699)
    - Wa, 1896-1928 (Box 24, Folder 700)
    - Wade, Margaret, 1901, undated (Box 24, Folder 701)
    - Walbek, A., 1929, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 702)
    - Waldo, Marie H., Undated (Box 24, Folder 703)
    - Waldo, P.M. (Box 24, Folder 703)
    - Wales, Enid Scarrett, Undated (Box 24, Folder 704)
    - Walker, Evelyn, 1898, 1910 (Box 24, Folder 705)
    - Walker, Exene S. (Mrs. Francis A.), 1889, 1890, 1894, 1898, undated (Box 24, Folder 706)
    - Walker, Francis A., 1890-1895 (Box 24, Folder 707)
    - Wambaugh, Sarah, 1924, 1928 (Box 24, Folder 708)
    - Ward, Anna H., 1896-1923, undated (Box 24, Folder 709)
    - Ward, Frances M., 1910, 1911, undated (Box 24, Folder 710)
    - Ward, Herbert D., 1899-1901, undated (Box 24, Folder 711)
    - Ward, Mary Alden, 1905, 1908 (Box 24, Folder 712)
    - Watchorn, Robert, 1906-1908 (Box 24, Folder 713)
    - Waters, Hilda, 1918, 1921 (Box 24, Folder 714)
    - We-Wh, 1893-1922 (Box 24, Folder 715)
    - Webb, Nellie S. (Mrs. James A. Jr.), 1903-1911, undated (Box 24, Folder 716-719)
    - Webber, Grace, 1901-1905 (Box 24, Folder 720)
    - Webster, Minna Hortense, 1896 (Box 24, Folder 721)
    - Welles, Anna F. (Mrs. F.R.), 1905-1915, undated (Box 24, Folder 722)
    - Welles, Carlotta (Box 24, Folder 722)
    - Welles, F.R. (Box 24, Folder 722)
    - Welles, Paul (Box 24, Folder 722)
    - Welles, Robert (Box 24, Folder 722)
    - Wells, Louisa, 1904-1907 (Box 24, Folder 723)
    - Wells, R.G. (Box 24, Folder 723)
    - West, Clara Linforth, 1903-1915, undated (Box 24, Folder 724)
    - Wetherell, Caroline, 1897 (Box 24, Folder 725)
    - Wheeler, Willard H., 1894 (Box 24, Folder 726)
    - Whitcomb, Anna G., 1907-1929 (Box 24, Folder 727)
    - Whitcomb, Annabell cook (Box 24, Folder 727)
    - Whitcomb, Elizabeth S., 1906-1909, undated (Box 24, Folder 728)
    - White, Eliza Orne, 1894-1908 (Box 24, Folder 729)
    - White, Grace Jay (Box 24, Folder 729)
    - Whitin, Sarah E. (Mrs. J.C.), 1895-1916 (Box 24, Folder 730)
    - Whiting, Agnes Mary, 1894-1911, undated (Box 24, Folder 731)
    - Whiting, Ann C. (Box 24, Folder 731)
    - Whiting, Eliza R. (Box 24, Folder 731)
    - Whiting, Margaret C. (Box 24, Folder 731)
    - Whiting, Sarah F. (Box 24, Folder 731)
    - Whiting, Mrs. William F. (Box 24, Folder 731)
    - Whiting, Lilian, 1896-1924, undated (Box 24, Folder 732-734)
    - Whitman, Alix (Mrs. George), 1913-1928 (Box 24, Folder 735)
    - Whitman, Leona E. (Box 24, Folder 735)
    - Whitney, Joseph Newcomb, 1890, 1896, 1918 (Box 24, Folder 736)
    - Wi, 1885-1932 (Box 24, Folder 737)
    - Wiggin, Kate Douglas, Undated (Box 24, Folder 738)
    - Williams, Mary E., 1891 (Box 24, Folder 739)
    - Williams, Talcott, 1905-1910 (Box 24, Folder 740)
    - Williston, Elizabeth, 1893-1899, undated (Box 24, Folder 741)
    - Williston, Lucy (Box 24, Folder 741)
    - Williston, Sarah T. (Box 24, Folder 741)
    - Wills, Frank J., 1908-1909 (Box 25, Folder 742)
    - Winslow, Helen M., 1898-1911, undated (Box 25, Folder 743)
      See also: box 106, folder 321.
    - Wo-Wy, 1889-1931 (Box 25, Folder 744)
    - Wolff, Stanley L., Circa 1905-1908, undated (Box 25, Folder 745)
    - Wood, Bertha D. (Mrs. Guilford S.), 1901-1904, undated (Box 25, Folder 746)
    - Wood, Elizabeth Dearing, 1909-1912 (Box 25, Folder 747)
    - Wood, Ella M., 1930-1932, undated (Box 25, Folder 748)
    - Woodbury, G.E., 1905 (Box 25, Folder 749)
    - Woolley, Mary E., 1903-1921, undated (Box 25, Folder 750)
    - Wortman, Doris, 1904-1909 (Box 25, Folder 751)
    - Wright, John H., 1888-1916 (Box 25, Folder 752)
    - Wright, Mary Tappan (Mrs. John H.) (Box 25, Folder 752)
    - Wynne, Madelene Yale, 1897-1909 (Box 25, Folder 753)
    - X-Y-Z, 1893-1931 (Box 25, Folder 754)
    - Young, Anna M., 1905-1912, undated (Box 25, Folder 755-756)
    - Young, Joan, 1910, 1911 (Box 25, Folder 757)
    - Young, Stark, 1916-1925 (Box 25, Folder 758)
    - Zug, George Breed, 1894-1902, undated (Box 25, Folder 759)
    - Unidentified letter of intimate character found in Amherst address book, 1892 (Box 25, Folder 760)
    - Unidentified, 1888-1930 (Box 25, Folder 761)
  - Family Correspondence
    - Allen, Enid Capwell, Undated (Box 26, Folder 762)
    - Aschenbach, Marion S.L., 1920-1923 (Box 26, Folder 763)
    - Avery, Clara A., 1897 (Box 26, Folder 764)
    - Avery, Susan H., 1884 (Box 26, Folder 764)
    - Avery, Susan Look, 1891-1909 (Box 26, Folder 764)
    - Bagg, Ernest N., 1891 (Box 26, Folder 765)
    - Bingham, Millicent Todd, 1883-1904 December (Box 26, Folder 766-792)
    - Bingham, Millicent Todd, 1905-1921 March (Box 27, Folder 793-819)
    - Bingham, Millicent Todd, 1921 April-1929 December (Box 28, Folder 820-846)
    - Bingham, Millicent Todd, 1930 January-1932 Oct, undated (Box 29, Folder 847-852)
    - Bingham, Walter Van Dyke, 1920-1932 (Box 29, Folder 853-855)
    - Capwell, Charles A., 1891-1912 (Box 29, Folder 856)
    - Capwell, Irene S. (Box 29, Folder 856)
    - Capwell, Julia A. (Box 29, Folder 856)
    - Chase, Persis F., 1899 (Box 29, Folder 857)
    - Compton, Naomi, 1879-1894 (Box 29, Folder 858-865)
    - Coonley, Avery, 1890-1891 (Box 29, Folder 866)
    - Coonley, Howard, 1891, 1899-1900, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 867)
    - Coonley, John Stuart, 1890-1905 (Box 29, Folder 868)
    - Coonley, Louisa Root (Box 29, Folder 868)
    - Coonley, Prentiss (Box 29, Folder 868)
    - Davies, Sarah Coonley (Mrs. William), 1890-1896 (Box 29, Folder 869)
    - Dickinson, C.E., 1903-1912 (Box 29, Folder 870)
    - Dickinson, C.N. (Box 29, Folder 870)
    - Dickinson, Mrs. E.B. (Box 29, Folder 870)
    - Dickinson, Marquis F. (Box 29, Folder 870)
    - Dickinson, Mattie Alice, 1893-1906 (Box 29, Folder 871)
    - Dickinson, S.L. (Mrs. C.) (Box 29, Folder 871)
    - Gardner, Anne Edes, 1898-1930 (Box 29, Folder 872)
    - Gardner, G.C. (Box 29, Folder 872)
    - Gardner, Eugene C., 1886-1913 (Box 29, Folder 873)
    - Gresham, Fanny Todd, 1912, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 874)
    - Harnot, Esse B., 1887, 1911 (Box 29, Folder 875)
    - Harnot, W.J. (Box 29, Folder 875)
    - Hollis, Mary L. Coonley (Mrs. Thomas), 1888-1902 (Box 29, Folder 876)
    - Hurd, Frances B. (Mrs. Frank), 1900, undated (Box 29, Folder 877)
    - Hurd, Frank (Box 29, Folder 877)
    - Ingersoll, Edward P., 1889 (Box 29, Folder 878)
    - Ingersoll, Helen A. (Mrs. Edward P.) (Box 29, Folder 878)
    - Kent, Daniel, 1905 (Box 29, Folder 879)
    - Kent, Everett E., 1912, 1920 (Box 29, Folder 880)
    - Kent, Georgia Tyler (Mrs. Daniel), 1903, 1905, undated (Box 29, Folder 881)
    - Kent, Mary Wilder, 1897-1908, undated (Box 29, Folder 882)
    - Kent, Rachel (Box 29, Folder 882)
    - Loomis, Achsie A. (Mrs. Mahlon), 1879 (Box 29, Folder 883)
    - Loomis, B., 1893, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 884)
    - Loomis, Battell (Box 30, Folder 884)
    - Loomis, Cornwall, Undated (Box 30, Folder 885)
    - Loomis, Eben J., 1879 July-1911 (Box 30, Folder 886-915)
    - Loomis, Eben J. and Marry W.: typed copies, 1880-1900 (Box 30, Folder 916)
    - Loomis, George C., 1925-1926 (Box 30, Folder 917)
    - Loomis, Grace L., 1910 (Box 30, Folder 918)
    - Loomis, Harriet Elwell Bagg (Mrs. Joseph S.), 1879-1915 (Box 30, Folder 919)
    - Loomis, Mary A., 1879 March-1884 June (Box 31, Folder 920-944)
    - Loomis, Mary A., 1884 July-1888 April (Box 32, Folder 945-968)
    - Loomis, Mary A., 1888 May-1889 November (Box 33, Folder 969-978)
    - Loomis, Mary A., 1890 March-1903 February (Box 34, Folder 979-1007)
    - Loomis, Mary A., 1903 March-1910 May, undated (Box 35, Folder 1008-1024)
    - Loomis, Nannie Gould, 1924 (Box 35, Folder 1025)
    - Loomis, Sarah E., 1879-1888 (Box 35, Folder 1026)
    - Loomis, Wilbur E., 1904, 1905 (Box 35, Folder 1027)
    - Loomis family, 1904-1932, undated (Box 35, Folder 1028)
    - Loomis Family Association, 1905-1929, undated (Box 35, Folder 1029)
    - Mason, Clara M. (Mrs. William A.), 1889 (Box 35, Folder 1030)
    - Parsons, Edward S., 1893-1905 (Box 35, Folder 1031)
    - Parsons, Katherine, 1891 (Box 35, Folder 1031)
    - Peck, Ella, 1880-1912 (Box 35, Folder 1032)
    - Peck, Frances M.J. (Mrs. David) (Box 35, Folder 1032)
    - Peck, Mr. and Mrs. Warren D. (Box 35, Folder 1032)
    - Robinson, Helen Avery, 1932 (Box 35, Folder 1033)
    - Schober, Mr. and Mrs. William B., 1917-1932 (Box 35, Folder 1034)
    - Shanklin, Gertrude Avery, 1891-1910 (Box 35, Folder 1035)
    - Shanklin, William A. (Box 35, Folder 1035)
    - Shaw, Joseph Alden, 1893 (Box 35, Folder 1036)
    - Sheip, Ella B., 1907-1908, 1916 (Box 35, Folder 1037)
    - Sheip, Henry H. (Box 35, Folder 1037)
    - Smith, Vina [Hedden?], 1880, 1888 (Box 35, Folder 1038)
    - Stearns, Annabel Alden, 1909 (Box 35, Folder 1039)
    - Stearns, Arthur B. (Box 35, Folder 1039)
    - Stevens, Flora E., 1902 (Box 35, Folder 1040)
    - Todd, Cornelia A., 1879-1889 (Box 35, Folder 1041)
    - Todd, Delbert (Box 35, Folder 1041)
    - Todd, David Peck, 1879 June 19-1882 December 26 (Box 35, Folder 1042-1046)
    - Todd, David Peck, 1883 April-1905 March (Box 36, Folder 1047-1074)
    - Todd, David Peck, 1905 July-1931 Dec, undated (Box 37, Folder 1075-1087)
    - Todd, Harriet, 1879, 1880 (Box 37, Folder 1088)
    - Todd, Sereno Edwards, Jr. (Box 37, Folder 1088)
    - Ward, Henry A., 1899-1904 (Box 37, Folder 1089)
    - Ward, Lydia Avery Coonley, 1888-1913 (Box 37, Folder 1090-1099)
    - Wilder, Constance Perley, 1900-1930 (Box 37, Folder 1100)
    - Wilder, Esther F., 1883-1923, undated (Box 38, Folder 1101-1105)
    - Wilder, Herbert Augustus, 1883-1923 (Box 38, Folder 1106-1108)
      See also: box 124, folder 75.
    - Wilder, Margaret T., 1899-1909 (Box 38, Folder 1109)
    - Wilder, Mary W.F. Jones, 1879-1893 (Box 38, Folder 1110)
      See also: box 3, folder 82.
    - Wilder, Sara B., 1890 (Box 38, Folder 1111)
    - Wilder, Sarah, 1895 (Box 38, Folder 1111)
    - Wilder family, Undated (Box 38, Folder 1112)
    - Wind, H.N., 1879 (Box 38, Folder 1113)
- Notebooks and Diaries, 1878-1932; Series III; 5.75 linear feet (14 boxes)
  NOTEBOOKS AND DIARIES has six sections: Diaries, Journals, Notebooks, Address Books, Appointment Books, and Miscellaneous. Each is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Diaries and journals, Series III, boxes 39-48, are available on microfilm. Patrons must use FILM HM 149 instead of the originals.
  - Diaries
    Patrons must use film HM 149.
    - 1879-1886 (Box 39, Folder 1-8, Reel 1U)
    - 1887-1893 (Box 40, Folder 9-16, Reel 2U)
    - 1894-1899 (Box 41, Folder 17-22, Reel 3U)
      The Bills payable section of Mabel Loomis Todd's 1897 diary may have been written by David Peck Todd in 1907. The original processor of the David Peck Todd papers included a folder (box 108, folder 56) for Todd's 1907 diary with the following note: "DPT diary 1907, see MLT 1897 diary (reused)." Manuscripts and Archive staff have been unable to locate a David Peck Todd diary for 1907, but believe the note refers to the Bills Payable section of Mabel Loomis Todd's 1897 diary in the Mabel Loomis Todd papers, MS 496C, Series III, box 41, folder 20.
    - 1900-1905 (Box 42, Folder 23-28, Reel 4U)
    - 1906-1911 (Box 43, Folder 29-34, Reel 5U)
    - 1912-1917 (Box 44, Folder 35-40, Reel 6U)
    - 1917-1932 (Box 45, Folder 41-44, Reel 6U, Reel 7U)
  - Journals
    - 1871 February 5-1885 May 25 (Box 45, Folder 45, Reel 7U)
    - 1871 June 8-1875 November 9 (Box 45, Folder 46, Reel 7U)
    - 1875 November 10-1879 March 5 (Box 45, Folder 47, Reel 7U)
    - Notes on MLT's Journal, 1879 March 25-1885 May 25 (Box 46, Folder 48, Reel 8U)
    - "Millicent's Life", Vols. I-IV, 1879-1885 (Box 46, Folder 49-51, Reel 8U)
    - 1879 March 25-1885 May 25 (Box 46, Folder 52, Reel 8U)
    - 1885 June 7-September 27 (Box 46, Folder 53, Reel 8U)
    - 1885 November 10-1896 March 31 (Box 46, Folder 54, Reel 8U)
    - 1887 June 11- August 21 (Box 46, Folder 55, Reel 8U)
    - 1887 August 27-November 7 (Box 46, Folder 56, Reel 8U)
      Typed excerpts, 1887 Sep 6-Sep 27.
    - 1892 March 25-May 3 (Box 47, Folder 57, Reel 9U)
    - 1896 April-July (Box 47, Folder 58, Reel 9U)
    - 1896 July-November (Box 47, Folder 59, Reel 9U)
      Typed excerpts, 1896 Aug 10-Aug 14.
    - Vol. VIII, 1897 April-1900 May (Box 47, Folder 60, Reel 9U)
      Typed excepts, 1900 May.
    - Vol IX, 1900 May-1901 April (Box 47, Folder 61, Reel 9U)
    - 1901 April 18-1902 May 22 (Box 47, Folder 62, Reel 9U)
    - 1902 July 7-1907 August 8 (Box 48, Folder 63, Reel 9U)
    - 1907 August 9-1927 April 8 (Box 48, Folder 64, Reel 9U)
    - 1927 May 21-1932 October 1 (Box 48, Folder 65, Reel 9U)
  - Notebooks
    - Collection of MLT's random thoughts, 1875 (Box 48, Folder 66, Reel 9U)
    - Notes on books, Vol. I, 1875 (Box 48, Folder 67, Reel 9U)
    - Notes on books, Vol. II, 1882 (Box 48, Folder 68, Reel 9U)
    - "Decorative suggestions", 1882 March (Box 48, Folder 69, Reel 9U)
    - Notes on books, Vols. III-IV, 1883-1888 (Box 49, Folder 70-71)
    - Short character sketches, 1887 (Box 49, Folder 72)
    - List of things to do, 1892-1894 (Box 49, Folder 73-74)
    - List of books given by family members as gifts, 1897-1913 (Box 49, Folder 75)
    - "Tripoli", 1900 May (Box 49, Folder 76)
    - Christmas card lists, 1903-1910 (Box 49, Folder 77-78)
    - Commonplace book, 1905 (Box 49, Folder 79)
    - Record of correspondence, 1907 (Box 49, Folder 80)
    - Fairhaven, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 81)
    - "Quotations from Clement's Poem on Mars", 1909 (Box 49, Folder 82)
    - Bridge rules, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 83)